dailymoss.com 2016-06-28

# Privacy Policy - The DailyMoss - Short stories and amusing lists from IndiaThe DailyMoss – Short stories and amusing lists from India

##### **The DailyMoss Privacy Policy**

_The DailyMoss_ respects the privacy of the readers/users of our website and services and we are committed to protecting it. We have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, and make use of personal information.

##### **Email Communication**

Your email address will never be shared with third-party without your permission. Sometimes, you may receive a newsletter or an email on our service. We collect your email when you subscribe to our website for weekly newsletter where you also have the option to unsubscribe any time you want.

##### **Cookies & Third-Party Advertisements**

The third-party companies can serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

##### **Cookie Policy**

We use cookies to enhance user experience. When you visit our website, your browsing patterns will be tracked in order to identify which pages are frequently visited and also to ensure that our site works efficiently. Most web browsers automatically accept ‘cookies’. However, you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies at any time, if preferred.

##### **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

_The DailyMoss_ reserves the right to change the privacy policy from time to time and it will be communicated.

_This policy was last updated on January 17 2015._
